[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Iron?", "correct_answer": "Fe", "incorrect_answers": ["I", "Ir", "Fi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Hooded Seal is a marine mammal that populates this geographic area.", "correct_answer": "Central and western North Atlantic", "incorrect_answers": ["North and northeast Pacific", "All of these", "North Indian Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you ping a network node, which protocol is being utilized?", "correct_answer": "ICMP", "incorrect_answers": ["RIP", "ICBM", "ARP"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Jake find in Hollis pond in the film Chinatown?", "correct_answer": "A pair of glasses", "incorrect_answers": ["A wallet", "A picture of Evelyn", "A gun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Italian singer, who  won the San Remo Music Festival twice, became popular in the United States in the 1950s with his song Volare.", "correct_answer": "Domenico Modugno", "incorrect_answers": ["Rossano Brazzi", "Luigi Tenco", "Peppino Gagliardi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What day of the week is associated with the pink color in Thailand?", "correct_answer": "Tuesday", "incorrect_answers": ["Friday", "Saturday", "Monday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was professional wrestler Triple H born in Massachusetts?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You are stranded on an island and start drinking water from the ocean because there is no other water source. What state will this put your cells in, and what will happen to you?", "correct_answer": "hypertonic; dehydrate", "incorrect_answers": ["hypotonic; rehydrate", "isotonic; be in the same state", "hypotonic; become sick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Labrador breed comes in 3 different colors.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The line Behold Mother, I make all things new that Jesus speaks in the 2004 movie The Passion of the Christ is taken from what book of the New Testament?", "correct_answer": "Book of Revelation", "incorrect_answers": ["Gospel of Mark", "Gospel of Luke", "Acts of the Apostles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient of the traditional Vietnamese dish Tiet canh?", "correct_answer": "Blood", "incorrect_answers": ["Beet", "Tomatoes", "Red pepper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the natural oil produced by human skin called?", "correct_answer": "Sebum", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Sebatiol", "Cutaneous oil"]}]